{
    "questions" : [
        {
            "question" : "A trifoliate plant that is a national symbol of Ireland",
            "correct_answer" : "Shamrock",
            "incorrect_answers" : ["Pepperwort","Water Clover","Lucky clover"]
        },
        {
            "question" : "In what year was the first celebration of St. Patrick’s Day in the United States?",
            "correct_answer" : "1737",
            "incorrect_answers" : ["1726","1903","1640"]
        },
        {
            "question" : "What is the birth name of St. Patrick?",
            "correct_answer" : "Maewyn Succat",
            "incorrect_answers" : ["Patricius","Patrick Celestine","Benignus"]
        },
        {
            "question" : "What was the original national color of Ireland during St. Patrick’s Day?",
            "correct_answer" : "Blue",
            "incorrect_answers" : ["Yellow","Green","Red"]
        },
        {
            "question" : "Which of the following rock singers/bands is Irish?",
            "correct_answer" : "U2",
            "incorrect_answers" : ["Roxette","Falco","EuropeYellow"]
        },
        {
            "question" : "Name of the wooden walking stick of the Leprechaun",
            "correct_answer" : "Shillelagh",
            "incorrect_answers" : ["Makila","Alpenstock","Kebbie"]
        },
        {
            "question" : "What happens to you If you don't wear green on St. Patrick's Day?",
            "correct_answer" : "Get pinched",
            "incorrect_answers" : ["Not allowed at the parade","Bad luck for a year","Have nightmares"]
        },
        {
            "question" : "Doing which of the following is said to bring you good luck on St. Patrick's Day?",
            "correct_answer" : "None of these",
            "incorrect_answers" : ["Wearing green clothes","Drinking beer","Taking a bath in a river"]
        },
        {
            "question" : "Where was the first St. Patrick’s Day Parade celebrated in 1762?",
            "correct_answer" : "New York",
            "incorrect_answers" : ["Ireland","Canada","Boston"]
        },
        {
            "question" : "In what location is it rumored that leprechauns bury their pot of gold?",
            "correct_answer" : "The end of a rainbow",
            "incorrect_answers" : ["A river","A mountain","In a cave"]
        },        
        {
            "question" : "Where was St Patrick born?",
            "correct_answer" : "Wales",
            "incorrect_answers" : ["Dublin","Kerry","Cork"]
        },
        {
            "question" : "When is Samhain celebrated?",
            "correct_answer" : "November",
            "incorrect_answers" : ["September","May","December"]
        },
        {
            "question" : "What is the second most spoken language in Ireland",
            "correct_answer" : "Polish",
            "incorrect_answers" : ["English","Irish","Gaelic"]
        },
        {
            "question" : "Where is Guinness consumed the most in the world?",
            "correct_answer" : "Nigeria",
            "incorrect_answers" : ["The United States","Argentina","Ireland"]
        },
        {
            "question" : "What is the national symbol of Ireland?",
            "correct_answer" : "Harp",
            "incorrect_answers" : ["Shamrock","Dairy Cow","St Patrick and Snakes"]
        },
        {
            "question" : "Which famous saint is buried in Ireland",
            "correct_answer" : "St Patrick",
            "incorrect_answers" : ["St Nicholas","St Sebastian","St Francis"]
        },
        {
            "question" : "What is a protective tradition in Ireland?",
            "correct_answer" : "Making a Brigid's cross to hang on the door",
            "incorrect_answers" : ["Throwing a glass of whiskey in the fire","Leaving gold jewellry in a basket by the door","Burning paper snakes"]
        },
        {
            "question" : "What superstition brings bad luck in Ireland?",
            "correct_answer" : "Seeing a lone magpie",
            "incorrect_answers" : ["Going to the funeral of a stranger","Having red hair","Saying leprechaun when drunk"]
        },
        {
            "question" : "Where are fairies said to be found in Ireland?",
            "correct_answer" : "In a lonely Hawthorne tree",
            "incorrect_answers" : ["In rocky quarries","In a field of clovers","On farm land"]
        },
        {
            "question" : "For good luck, what is a common Irish tradition?",
            "correct_answer" : "Lighting a candle",
            "incorrect_answers" : ["Dancing a jig","Singing to St Patrick","Drink a shot of whiskey"]
        },        
        {
            "question" : "Bandon, born Graham William Walker is better known professionally as?",
            "correct_answer" : "Graham Norton",
            "incorrect_answers" : ["Stephan Nolan","Brendan O'Connor",""]
        },
        {
            "question" : "Which Limerick-born broadcaster was associated with the Eurovision Song Contest for many years, ending their connection in 2008?",
            "correct_answer" : "Sir Terry Wogan",
            "incorrect_answers" : ["Laura Whitmore","Gerry Ryan",""]
        },
        {
            "question" : "What day was consider lucky to sow potatoes?",
            "correct_answer" : "Good Friday",
            "incorrect_answers" : ["Easter Sunday","Maundy Thursday",""]
        },
        {
            "question" : "What is the significance of a horse or donkey shoe nailed above the door in an Irish house?",
            "correct_answer" : "To bring good luck",
            "incorrect_answers" : ["Stables","To show the occupants lost a horse in battle",""]
        },
        {
            "question" : "On what day of the week is it considered unlucky to cut your fingernails?",
            "correct_answer" : "Sunday",
            "incorrect_answers" : ["Wednesday","Friday",""]
        },
        {
            "question" : "What is a traditional flute made from?",
            "correct_answer" : "Tin",
            "incorrect_answers" : ["Wood","Bone",""]
        },
        {
            "question" : "What is a bodhran?",
            "correct_answer" : "A drum",
            "incorrect_answers" : ["A pie","A traditional Irish drink",""]
        },
        {
            "question" : "In what year did Guinness formally adopt the harp as its symbol?",
            "correct_answer" : "1962",
            "incorrect_answers" : ["1970","1974",""]
        },
        {
            "question" : "Where was 'Waking Ned' filmed?",
            "correct_answer" : "Isle of Man",
            "incorrect_answers" : ["Isle of White","Cork",""]
        },
        {
            "question" : "Which part of Ireland is Coddle traditionally asscociated with?",
            "correct_answer" : "Dublin",
            "incorrect_answers" : ["Sligo","Donegal",""]
        }
    ]
}